Inventory of the Archibald Woods Papers 1777-1893, 1783-1846
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Henry F. Barnand, Tyler County, Virginia, [West Virginia] to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 7 January 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1838)
  Inquires about rental of farm. Apologizes for incident of previous year.
- Mary Hanes, Tyler County, Virginia to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Ohi[o] County, Virginia[West Virginia], 11 January 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1839)
  Asks permission to live on one acre of Woods' land.
- [Archibald Woods] to I[saac] Leffler, n.p., 14 January 1833., 1 page. Copy of AL. (Folder 1840)
  Concerning Leffler's chances for election to Congress and the election of directors to the Northwestern Bank of Virginia.
- [Archibald Woods] to [John McCoy], 17 January 1833., 1 page. Copy of AL. (Folder 1841)
  Concerns Northwestern Bank of Virginia.
- Isaac Leffler, n.p., to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], January 1833., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1842)
  Have gained a most significant victory in the lower house over the Virginia nullifiers. Defeated by one vote. We shall either run Tyler or McCoy for the Senate...we shall not likely [rally?] Tyler. The west and middle regions are well organized and we can elect him to a certainty.., resolved to put down these southern notions. In Virginia much is to be done in the election of a senator. Rives is with us and if we get Tyler we are safe, at the request of several western members on Thursday last I addressed a letter to Tyler, to know his sentiments on secession and nullification. This evening I send his answer. Gives defense on appointment of directors to Northwestern Bank. Determined about spring election.
- E[dgar] C[ampbell] Wilson, n.p., to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 22 January 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1843)
  Possibilities for election [to Congress.]
- E[dgar] C[ampbell] Wilson, n.p., A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 26 January 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1844)
  Chances for election.
- Mary Woods, Mount Prospect, Illinois? to Brother [in-law] Hamilton Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 28 January [1833]., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1845)
  Family news. Concerned about his health. Questions about a debt and education of children
- James Smith, [Roseville, Indiana] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 29 January 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1846)
  Taking depositions to prove military service.
- Peter Anshutz, Powhatan Point, [Ohio] to Archi[bal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 30 January 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1847)
  Would like to take a house he is building for Woods.
- A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia] to Joseph McCoy, n.p., 5 February 1833., 1 page. Copy of LS. (Folder 1848)
  Terms for an agreement on land to avoid a lawsuit.
  Includes, AM, of notes concerning [Archibald Woods'] terms of settlement with Joseph McCoy. 1 page.
- E[dgar] C[ampbell] Wilson,[Morgantown, Virginia] [West Virginia], to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 9 February 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1849)
  Candidacy for Congress.
- Sam[ue]l H. Guthrie, Woodsfield, [Ohio], to Daniel Peck, St. Clairsville, Ohio, 12 February 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1850)
  Dispute with Archibald Woods.
- H. F. Reeny, Montezuma, [Parke, County, Indiana], to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 16 February 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1851)
  Has application to buy Woods' land.
- Dan[ie]l Peck, St. Clairsville, [Ohio], to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia, 18 February 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1852)
  Guthrie cannot prepare himself to fulfill compromise offered.
- Archi[bal]d Woods, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to John McLure, Washington, [D.C.], 19 February 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1853)
  Asks for copy of patent. Received $26,500 in part of money stolen from [Northwestern Bank of Virginia]. Lists candidates for Congress.
  Includes, ALS, of John McLure, n.p., to A[rchibald] Woods, n.p. Needs evidence to secure copy of a patent. 1 page.
- J. B. Roberts, Whe[eling, [Virginia][West Virginia] to Archable [Archibald] Woods, n.p., 23 February 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1854)
  Has concluded to take Powhatan Place at Captina.
- C. D. Knox, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods,[Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 25 February 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1855)
  Will endorse a note for W[illia]m B. King on certain conditions.
- C. D. Knox, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods,[Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 26 February 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1856)
  Asks that Woods make deed to Martha [(Woods) Knox].
- Dan[ie]l Peck, St. Clairsville [Ohio], to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 5 March 1833., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1857)
  Thinks Woods need not fear any great difficulty with Guthrie. Equalizing board sits in June.
- H. F. Feeny, Montezuma, [Parke County, Indiana] to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 15 March 1833., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1858)
  Sold Woods' land in Vigo County to Chauncey Rose. Thomas Woods' land has been sold for taxes. County in distressed situation for want of money. Failure of crops last two years.
- E[dgar] C[ampbell] Wilson, Morgantown, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 16 March 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1859)
  Prospects for election to Congress.
- Estimate of lands sold by Archibald Woods to Samuel H. Gutherie, 25 March 1833., 1 page. M. (Folder 1860)
- A. D. Clarke, Fish Creek, [?], to Archib[al]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 28 March 1833., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1861)
- Arthur Okey, Woodsfield, [Ohio] to Archable [Archibald] Woods, Wheeling, Ohi[o] County, Virginia[West Virginia], 7 April 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1862)
  Information on Samuel H. Githerie's business. Gave Woodman notice to settle note.
- C. Wells, to Archabel [Archibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 22 April 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1863)
  Request to borrow money.
- J. B. Roberts, Grand Gulph, to Archable [Archibald] Woods, Wheeling, Ohio County, Virginia [West Virginia], 23 April 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1864)
  Asks Woods to attend to note.
- J. Mallory, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia], 30 April 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1865)
  Needs to meet with Woods.
- J. B. Roberts, Grand Gulph, [?], to Archable [Archibald] Woods, Wheeling, Ohio County, Virginia [West Virginia], 2 May 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1866)
  Arrangements for settling with Woods.
- Michael Cresap, n.p., to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia], 4 May 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1867)
  Recommends individuals as magistrates and opposes Nicholas Wykert.
- Agnes Clark, Steubenville, [Ohio], to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 27 May [1833]., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1868)
  Asks for money due under Eugenius Wilson's will.
- [M. Woods], Mount Prospect near Pittsburgh [Pennsylvania] to Father Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], [5 June 1833?]., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1869)
  Lost horse in coal pit. Family news, (Letter is begun by Louisa [?])
- C. D. Knox, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods,[Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 7 June 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1870)
  Mr. Grafton and Mr. King have closed their bargin [bargain]. Sends reports of board of health, "I have this morning seen Doctor Houston an he informs that he has not heard of any new cases today."
- Arthur Okey, Woodsfield, [Ohio] to Archabld [Archibald] Woods, Wheeling, Ohio County, Virginia [West Virginia], 17 June 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1871)
  Have not brought money to Wheeling because of fear of the colerry [cholera] Gutherie is selling land.
- Charles D. Knox, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, [Virginia], 20 June 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1872)
  Sylvia [?] left at house of John F. Clarke things left by Mr. Paull. Encloses reports of Board of Health. "The ... sickness with two exceptions is confined to the immediate neighborhood of McConnell's old tan yard. I am informed that the old vats is full of water and all kinds of filth & that they have been in that situation for the last two years."
- M[ary] Woods, n.p., to mother Mrs. Anne Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 20 June [1833]., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1873)
  M[ary] Woods, n.p., to mother Mrs. Anne Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia]. Received letter from Dr. Houston. Trusts her Ann is obedient. Mr. Laurie preached his trial sermon.
- Daniel Peck, St. Clairsville, Ohio, to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia, 21 June 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1874)
  Mr. Ruggles and wife deeded lot to Gutherie. People are frightened of cholera. "If anyone dies in this neighborhood & wee [sic] have had a number of deaths, the person is rolled up in his bed, & bedclothes & his own clothes tumbled into a rough box, as soon as dead, & immediately buried." Guthrie will deed lots to Woods.
- Archi[bal]d Woods, n. p., to Zac[aria]s Jacob, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia], 29 June 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1875)
  Asks about distraining [detaining personal property for security of a debt] a wheat crop. Includes, ALS, of Jacob answering Woods questions. 1 page.
- H. F. Feeny, Montezuma, Parke County, [Indiana] to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia, 24 July 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1876)
  Report on tending to Woods' land.
  Includes, AMS, account of Woods with Feeny. 1 page.
- John C. Snider, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 24 July 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1877)
  Wishes to borrow six hundred dollars. Father will give deed of trust on property in Hagerstown, Maryland.
- M[ary (Woods)] Wilson, Salt Sulfer [Sulphur] Springs, to Arch[ibald] Woods, Ohio County, Virginia [West Virginia], 29 July 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1878)
  Describes trips to White Sulfer [Sulphur] Springs and salt Sulphur Springs.
- M. D. Washington, "Hills" [Ohio County, Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods, near Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia], 2 August 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1879)
  Asks to borrow fifty dollars.
- Rich[ar]d H. Henderson, Leesburg, [Virginia] to W[illia]m B. King, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 7 August 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1880)
  Letter of recommendation for N. Osburne as a tavern keeper.
- John [R. Cocke] Win[chester, Virginia] to W[illiam] B. King, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 7 August 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1881)
  Osburn keeps a first-rate tavern.
- J. T. Martin, Tridelphia, [?], to A[rchibald] Woods, n.p., 10 August 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1881A)
  Will build mill wheel for two dollars and fifty c[en]ts per foot.
- Copy of Resolution of trustees of Wheeling Lancasterian Academy that Samuel Sprigg and Archibald Woods be appointed a Committee to settle with Henry Sockman for rent of Know Hon Farm, 15 August 1833. (Folder 1882)
- Archi[bal]d Woods, n.p. to Isaac S. Seman, n.p., 15 August 1833., 1 page. AcyS of ALS. (Folder 1883)
  Concerns terms of rental of stores and warehouse at Powhatan.
- [I or J] List, New York, [New York] to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Pres[iden]t N[orth] W[est] B[an]k, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 31 August 1833., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1884)
- [Archibald Woods] to T. Ewing, n.p., [September 1833?]., 3 pages. Copy of AL. (Folder 1885)
  Answer to inquiries about North Western Bank of Virginia.
- John Wells, n.p. to Archibald Woods, n.p., 2 September 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1886)
  Request to borrow two thousand dollars from Wheeling Bank.
- J. T. Martin, Tridelphia, [?], to A[rchibald] Woods, Greenfield [Ohio County?, Virginia] [West Virginia], 25 September 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1887)
  Progress on building of grist mill.
- H. F. Feeny, Montezuma, Virginia [Indiana], to Archbold [Archibald] Wood[s], Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 26 October 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1888)
  Payment by [?] Rose for Woods' property is in hands of Warren & Co., to Terra Haute. Much sickness few cases of cholera.
- Samuel H. Gutherie, Woodsfield, [Ohio], to Arch[ibal]d Woods, n.p., 1 November 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1888A)
  W[illia]m Crawford's house and lot were not sold, but an empty lot between his house and Randolph Tavern was sold, as was his farm.
- M. Woods, [Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania] to Archibald Woods, care of Geo[rge] W[ashington] Wilson, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], [4 November 1833]., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1889)
  Concern over accident involving [Ann (Poage) Woods] [Washington, and Franklin Woods?]
- R. W. Washington, [Wheeling, Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods,[Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 25 November 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1890)
  Encloses mothers' receipt for money lent her by Woods.
- Edgar C. Wilson, [Washington, D.C.] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 2 December 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1891)
  Jackson "goes full tilt against the bank."
- James Young, West Philad[elphi]a, Pennsylvania to A[rchibald] Woods, President of North Western Bank of Virginia [West Virginia], 9 December 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1892)
  Wants to know if bank robbers are caught.
- [?] Washington [D.C.] to W[illia]m T. Barry, n.p., 11 December 1833., 1 page. L. (Folder 1893)
  National Road Stage has incurred extra expense in fulfilling mail contract. Asks compensation.
- Jno. B. Smith, Stinersville, [Ohio], to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 14 December 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1894)
  Wants to rent house for grocery at Powhatan Point. Asks Woods advice.
- Arthur Okey, Woodsfield, [Ohio], to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 22 December 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1895)
  Has applicants for Thomas Woods' heirs' land.
- John McLure, Richmond, [Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 27 December 1833., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1896)
  Committee report on courthouse is unfavorable. May be reversed and brought before House Of Delegates. Will present memorial concerning Northwestern Bank. Floyd promised appointment but he and Council are not speaking. Large meeting in Richmond concerning deposits. [Benjamin Watkins] Leigh spoke.
- Absalom Ridgely, Short Creek, Ohio County, Virginia to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Ohio County, [Virginia] [West Virginia], 30 December 1833., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1897)
  Woods to vote for him.
- Cowen & Carroll per C. C. Carroll to [?], n.d., 1 page. LS. (Folder 1898)
  Concerns sale of land for taxes.
- E[dgar] C[ampbelI] Wilson,[Washington, D.C.] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia, 4 January 1834. (Folder 1899)
  Encloses memorials. [Thomas Hart] Benton is "pouring out vials of his wrath upon Clay and the bank."
- H[amilton] Woods, Washington, [D.C.] to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 14 [January 1814?]., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1900)
  Trip to Washington. Heard Calhoun speak. Description of city.
- Arthur Okey, Woodsfield, [Ohio] to Archabled [Archibald] Woods, near Wheeling, Ohio County, Virginia [West Virginia], 20 January 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1901)
  Terms prospective tenant would like for leasing land. Opinion on land.
- H[amilton] Woods, Washington, [D.C.], to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 20 January 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1902)
  Heard [William Cabell] Rives deliver speech on removal of deposits.
- Hamilton Woods, Richmond, [Virginia] to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 3 February 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1903)
  Courthouse questions to be brought up any day. Private committee recommended division of county.
- Sam[ue]l H. Guthrie, Woodsfield, [Ohio] to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 7 February 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1904)
  Send form for Woods' release mortgages by Guthrie.
- David Person, Woodsfield, [Ohio] to Archi[bald] Woods, n.p., 8 February 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1905)
  Recommends W[illia]m H. McNabb for loan with a lot as security.
  Includes, ALS, of W[illia]m H. McNabb stating that he will mortgage lot with a lot nearly owns. 1 page.
- James Rankin, n.p., to Arche [Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 10 July 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1906)
  Promises not to cut any timber contrary to Woods' wishes.
- Jer[emiah] Hollister, to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 12 February 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1907)
  Lots sold by Samuel H. Gutherie to the Methodist Episcopal Church.
- John Minder [Powhatan P.O., Ohio] to Arch[ibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 16 February 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1908)
  Desires to sell stock in Northwestern Bank of Wheeling.
- A.D. Clarke, n.p., to Archib[al]d Woods, n.p., 5 March 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1909)
  Cannot pay money owed.
- Charles Wells, n.p., to Archable [Archibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], March 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1910)
  Excuse for not paying note.
- Arthur Okey, Woodsfield, [Ohio] to Archabled [Archibald] Woods, Wheeling, Ohio County, Virginia [West Virginia], 12 March 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1911)
  Handling the rental of Woods' house for him.
- Charles D. Knox, Louisville, [Kentucky] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 19 March 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1912)
  Called on General Breckenridge and found he was dead. Called on nephew and heir James D. Breckenridge.
- H. F. Feeny Montezuma, Indiana, to Arch[i]b[al]d Woo[ds], Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 26 March 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1913)
  Pecuniary embarrassments of this section of the county. Sent copy of a of bill of legislature chartering bank and branches.
- Stout & Hull, Wheeling, [Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods, n.p., 5 April 1834., 1 page. L. (Folder 1914)
  Buying flour.
- D[aniel] Peck, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to [Archibald Woods], 12 April 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1915)
  James Moore will do surveying.
- Archi[bal]d Woods, n.p., to Directors of N[orth] W[estern] Bank of Virg[ini]a,1 May 1824., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1916)
  Resignation as President and Director.
- Joseph Hicks for Jonathan Binnager, Barnesville [Belmont County, Ohio] to Archibald Wood[s], Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 9 May 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1917)
  Binnager needs indulgence on money owed Woods for land. Vouches for him.
- A. D. Clarke, Fish Creek, Virginia [West Virginia] to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia], 20 May 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1918)
  Has two yokes for oxen for sale and a horse.
- P. Martin, Fishing Creek, Virginia [West Virginia], to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 26 May 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1919)
  Desires to borrow money from bank.
- Archi[bal]d Woods, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to Robert R. Levingston, Armstrong, Crawford County, Pennsylvania, 10 June 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1920)
  Offer to rent a house, steam mill etc. for a lumberyard.
- H. F. Feeny, Montezuma, [Indiana] to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 1 July 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1921)
  Relays information from [?] Rose concerning payment of a note. Commissioners authorized to negotiate the loan for our state bank and branches.
- Knox & McKee, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods,[Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 3 July 1834., 1 page. L. (Folder 1922)
  Payment on note and harsh policies of Northwestern Bank of Virginia.
- C. D. Knox, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods,[Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 11 July 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1923)
  Wants to have bank board convened to discount notes.
- R.W. Washington Highlands, [Ohio County, Virginia] [West Virginia], to Arch[ibal]d Woods, President of the North W[estern] Bank of Virginia, [Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 14 July 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1924)
  Unable to pay note.
- Archi[bal]d Woods, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to Joseph Smith, Roseville, Park[e] County, Indiana, 30 July 1834., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1925)
  Got judgment and execution against Fogle but no property could be found and Fogle died. Asks if son Thomas' land on Raccoon Creek could be leased. [H. F.] Feeny redeemed it. Some cases of cholera. J[ames?] Seman ill. Jacksonian politics.
- Howson Hooe, Bradly, [Brentvi1le, Virginia], to Arch[ibal]d Woods, near Wheeling, Ohio County, Virginia [West Virginia], 1 August 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1926)
  Market for slaves and horses.
- John Bowland, Bloomington, [Indiana] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 14 August 1834., 3 pages. ALS. (Folder 1927)
  Showed Woods' lands to [?] Scott. Will tend to taxes.
- H. F. Feeny, Montezuma, [Indiana], to Archibald Wood[s], Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 27 August 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1928)
  Has offered to buy land belonging to Thomas Woods' heirs.
- Z. Jacob, C.D. Knox, James W. Clemons, Jno. Kno[?], Committee to pay funeral honors for Lafayette, to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Ohio County, Virginia [West Virginia], 3 September 1834., 1 page. L. (Folder 1929)
  Asks Woods to be pallbearer.
- Isaac S. Seaman, Powhatan Pt., Ohio, to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 6 September 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1930)
  Daniel Steenrod wants to keep place five years longer if Woods will build stable and house or fix old one.
- Jacob Ash, Tyler County, Virginia, to Archibald Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 30 September 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1931)
  Has lost land under older title. Does not wish to sue Woods. Suggests referring matter to three men.
- Daniel Peck, St. Clairsville, [Ohio] to A[rchibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 1 October 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1932)
  Sends check.
- R. T. Berry, Martinsburgh, [Martinsburg], Virginia [West Virginia] to [?], 20 October 1834., 4 pages. ALS. (Folder 1933)
  Confirms death of addressee's mother. Words of religious consolation.
- Tho[ma]s P. Ray, to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia], 31 October 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1934)
  Notifies him of money still due by estate of Eugenius Wilson.
  Includes, AMS, receipt of Tho[ma]s P. Ray, surviving executor of Nimrod Evans to Archabald [Archibald] Woods. 1 page.
- C. P. Anshutz, Powhatan Point, [Ohio], to Arch[ibal]d Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], [1] November 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1935)
  David Lively wishes to rent Woods' tavern.
- E[dgar] C[ampbell] Wilson, Morgantown, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to Arch[ibald] Woods, Wheeling, Virginia [West Virginia], 12 November [1834]., 6 pages. ALS. (Folder 1936)
  Does not think Woods is liable on special warrantee deed to [Jacob] Ash. Wilson outlines his prospects for election. Measles prevail.
- James Maguire, Dillis Bottom, [Ohio], to [Archibald] Woods, near Whe[e]ling, [Virginia][West Virginia], 24 November 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1937)
  Ready to start boat.
- C. D. Knox, Wheeling, [Virginia] [West Virginia] to A[rchibald] Woods,[Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 25 November 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1938)
  Concerns gathering signatures.
- R.W. Washington, [Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], to A[rchibald] Woods, [Wheeling, Virginia] [West Virginia], 28 November 1834., 1 page. ALS. (Folder 1939)
  Needs to borrow money from Woods to pay off note at Bank if it cannot be renewed.
- H. F. Feeny, Senate Chamber, Indianapolis, [Indiana], to Archibald Wood[s], n.p., 6 December 1834., 2 pages. ALS. (Folder 1940)
  Will send money by safe opportunity. Has offer for lands owned by heirs of Thomas Woods.